

# Brayan Andrés Covaría

3153762685 6406999 covaria\_07@hotmail.com cra48#30-21 Bucaramanga

#### **Profile**

## **Computer and Systems Engineer**

UIS Systems Engineer interested in the continuous learning of new technologies, who has a responsible attitude to meet deadlines, with a high level of ability for teamwork, capable of analyzing and solving day-to-day problems, providing solutions that meet the customer's expectations. In the projects he's involved, takes into account the Development standards implemented by the company, regarding Database and Development. Moreover, performs unit tests (Developer Tests) and Documentation of the developed software product. Counts with 8 years of experience in leadership and software development using agile methodologies like Scrum, and using different technologies such as JAVA, Spring boot, Amazon AWS, Oracle, HTML5, Boostrap, JQuery.

## **Experience**

## **Engineer Lead**

Rappi Colombia September 2022- Current position

Bogotá - Colombia Sector: Tecnology

Lead engineer in charge of managing a team of developers to achieve objectives in projects that help the company prevent fraud by application users, using agile methodologies such as scrum, managing all the necessary resources to achieve the objectives, as well supporting the team and its junior developers in software development. We implement technologies such as java, spring boot, and amazon aws among others.

#### Specialized Engineer

Banco de la república October 2019 – September 2022

Bogotá - Colombia

Lead engineer who understands, manages and configures the software Application that collects information and calculates Colombia's foreign exchange balance. This management involves knowledge of software, installations and budget analysis, among other tasks.

Sector: Banca

#### Senior software development engineer

Beneficiar entidad cooperativa de ahorro y crédito April 2019 - September 2019

#### Bogotá - Colombia

Application software development Engineer who applies agile methodologies such as Scrum for financial entities.

#### Senior software development engineer

Electrosoftware Itda August 2016 - April 2019

#### **Bucaramanga-Colombia**

Sector: Electric Power

Sector: Financial Services

Software senior Engineer developing an App for the management of electrical grids in Santander, Colombia and Honduras. Implemented and supported Web Services in Delphi Seatle programming language, for sending information between the company's system and SAP technologies.

#### Software development engineer

Indra Colombia March 2015 - August 2016

#### **Bucaramanga-Colombia**

Sector: Software producers and distributors

System engineer who developed web and mobile applications using programming languages such as Java, Perl, Html5, Boostrap, and Javascript, among others.

Participated in a project with the cell phone manufacturer "Mywigo", where an initiative was carried out to monitor the internal operation of their equipment from a web application.

#### **Studies**

\_\_\_\_

#### **Educational background**

#### Bachelor's degree in Systems engineering

UIS (Universidad Industrial de Santander) March 2010 - December 2015

## Bachelor with emphasis on Systematized accounting

Corporación educativa minuto de Dios Colegio café Madrid February 2004 - November 2009

#### **Additional studies**

#### Computer's architecture

SENA January 2014 – January 2014

# Development of applications with graphical interface, event, class and object handling: java

#### Adobe Photoshop\_cs5

SENA January 2014 - January 2014

## Web design with adobe dreamweaver

SENA January 2014 - January 2014

## Application development with concurrent processing and menu-driven

applications: java

SENA January 2014 - January 2014

#### **English Beginner**

SENA January 2014 - January 2014

## Languages

**English** 

Fluency: B2

**Spanish** 

Native language- fluency: C2

#### **Skills**

- · Teamwork
- · Leadership
- Autonomous learning
- · Perception of systems and environment

#### **Tools**

 Solaris Angular · Java Spring Boot Delphi Oracle · .NET · Html React BOOTSTRAP Jquery

· Shell

Javascript